chowk.com 2011-06-01

# privacy-policy

Chowk respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our Web site. To that end, any personal information you provide to [Chowk.com](http://www.chowk.com/) will be known only to two parties: you and Chowk. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our pages and their features. Personal information includes your name, street and e-mail addresses, billing information, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here.

**Traffic data**

We also count, track and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites (e.g. tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the [Chowk.com](http://www.chowk.com/) site, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into aggregate data which is used for internal monitoring of the website and not shared with third parties.

**Use of Chowk cookies**

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies in a limited way to help deliver advertisements, to identify unique browsers that visit us and to track usage throughout our site.

**Chowk Interaction**

In order to post replies, Chowkwalas need to register using personal information including name, address, e-mail address. All personal information at Chowk is strictly confidential and Chowk does not resell or redistribute it in any way.

**Registration Details**

At the time readers register at Chowk, Chowk asks for a phone number so we can make an effort to contact you in connection with publication of your submission. We do not retain this information for any other purpose, nor do we sell, trade or otherwise disclose it to third parties.

**E-mail to a friend** feature

Chowk offers an e-mail a friend feature, allowing site visitors to send e-mail to friends to inform them about an interesting submission. In order for this feature to function, we ask for e-mail addresses for the recipient (so we know who to mail the message to) and from the sender (so we can tell the recipient who sent the e-mail). We do not store or save these addresses and you will not receive e-mail or other communications from Chowk or its partners as a result of having used this feature.   
We do not sell or redistribute Chowkwala membership list and will not send you e-mail at the address you provide, except for infrequent announcements relating to Chowk or as needed to resolve issues that may arise with your Chowk account. From time to time, Chowk may also email you about relevant events such as special issues, events etc. Chowk does not reuse or resell the list of registered users.

Participants at Chowk are expected to comply with the [InterAct! guidelines](http://www.chowk.com/interacts/guidelines) but we cannot control third parties' use of information you may choose to provide in such a public forum. For more information see the Chowk [registration page](http://www.chowk.com/signup).

**Other disclosure of personal information**

Chowk will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority.

**Other sites**

Chowk contains links to other sites on the Web and personal home pages. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other Web sites.

**Who can I ask if I have any additional questions?**

If you have any further questions or concerns about Chowk's privacy policies and use of personal information, please send them to [ ](mailto:editors%%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy84350%20=%20'5C'%20+%20'@';%20addy84350%20=%20addy84350%20+%20'chowk'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy84350%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy84350%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[editors@chowk.com](mailto:editors@chowk.com)
